<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WeRTutors</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="john_doe">John Doe</string>
    <string name="profile_picture">Profile Picture</string>
    <string name="Wertutors">WeRTutors</string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>

    <string name="nav_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="nav_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="nav_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="type_of_tutoring">Type of Tutoring</string>

    <string name="sipho">Sipho Mthethwa\n\nWork Experience:\n Sipho is a high school math teacher with over 7 years of experience in teaching advanced mathematics. He specializes in preparing students for national exams and has a track record of improving student performance through personalized tutoring.\n\nEducation:\nSipho holds a Bachelor’s degree in Education, specializing in Mathematics, from the University of Johannesburg.\n\nCourses and Certifications:\nCertified in Advanced Mathematical Pedagogy by the South African Council for Educators (SACE)\nCompleted online courses on Data Analysis in Education from Coursera.\n\nSkills:\nCurriculum development\nPersonalized learning strategies\nAdvanced calculus and algebra</string>

    <string name="zanele">Zanele Mhlongo\n\nWork Experience:\nZanele is a business and economics tutor with over 6 years of experience working with both high school and university students. She has helped many students understand complex economic theories and business strategies.\n\nEducation:\nZanele holds a Bachelor of Commerce in Economics from Durban University of Technology.\n\nCourses and Certifications:\nCompleted certification in Financial Analysis from Udemy\nCertified Economics Tutor by TutorABC.\n\nSkills:\nFinancial modeling\nMicro and macroeconomics\nBusiness management and consulting</string>

    <string name="kabelo">Kabelo Phiri\n\nWork Experience:\nKabelo is a skilled computer programming tutor with 5 years of experience. He focuses on teaching algorithms, data structures, and object-oriented programming. Kabelo has worked with students from beginner to advanced levels in coding.\n\nEducation:\nKabelo holds a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science from the University of Limpopo.\n\nCourses and Certifications:\nCompleted a Data Structures and Algorithms course from Udacity\nCertified Java Developer by Oracle University.\n\nSkills:\nObject-oriented programming\nAlgorithm optimization\nData structure design</string>

    <string name="lerato">Lerato Mokoena\n\nWork Experience:\nLerato is an experienced data scientist with a passion for data analytics and machine learning. She has 4 years of experience working in the tech industry and tutoring students in data science concepts.\n\nEducation:\nLerato holds a Master’s degree in Data Science from the University of Pretoria.\n\nCourses and Certifications:\nCompleted the Data Science Specialization on Coursera (offered by Johns Hopkins University)\nCertified in Machine Learning by Stanford University.\n\nSkills:\nPython programming\nMachine learning algorithms\nBig data analysis</string>

    <string name="sizwe">Sizwe Nkosi\n\nWork Experience:\nSizwe has a diverse background, having tutored in both mathematics and physical sciences for over 5 years. He is particularly interested in helping students excel in problem-solving and analytical thinking.\n\nEducation:\nSizwe holds a Bachelor’s degree in Mechanical Engineering from Durban University of Technology.\n\nCourses and Certifications:\nCertified in Fluid Mechanics by edX\nCompleted a course in Applied Mathematics from MIT OpenCourseWare.\n\nSkills:\nMechanical design\nPhysics and applied mathematics\nEngineering problem-solving</string>

    <string name="mbali">Mbali Mkhize\n\nWork Experience:\nMbali is a passionate educator with over 6 years of experience teaching physics and chemistry at both high school and university levels. She has helped students achieve remarkable improvements in their understanding of physical sciences through practical and theoretical learning techniques.\n\nEducation:\nMbali holds a Bachelor’s degree in Chemical Engineering from the University of KwaZulu-Natal.\n\nCourses and Certifications:\nCertified in Advanced Chemistry from Coursera\nCompleted a Physics Specialization from MIT OpenCourseWare.\n\nSkills:\nThermodynamics and chemical processes\nPhysics and chemistry tutoring\nProblem-solving and analytical thinking</string>

    <string name="ayanda">Ayanda Ndlovu\n\nWork Experience:\nAyanda is a history and geography enthusiast with a unique ability to make subjects engaging and relevant. With over 6 years of tutoring experience, she has helped students improve their knowledge of world history and geographic systems.\n\nEducation:\nAyanda holds a Bachelor’s degree in History and Geography from the University of Cape Town.\n\nCourses and Certifications:\nCertified in Geographic Information Systems (GIS) by Udemy\nCompleted an Advanced History Course from the University of Oxford Online.\n\nSkills:\nHistorical analysis\nGeography and environmental science\nCritical thinking and writing</string>

    <string name="bianca">Bianca Moodley\n\nWork Experience:\nBianca is a computer engineering specialist with a focus on hardware systems and software integration. She has over 5 years of tutoring experience in computer engineering topics, especially for university students.\n\nEducation:\nBianca holds a Master’s in Computer Engineering from Stellenbosch University.\n\nCourses and Certifications:\nCertified in Embedded Systems by Coursera\nCompleted a Machine Learning specialization from Stanford University.\n\nSkills:\nEmbedded systems\nArtificial intelligence\nSoftware engineering</string>

    <string name="christina">Christina Goncalves\n\nWork Experience:\nChristina is an expert in biology and environmental science with over 8 years of experience in tutoring high school and university students. She has a deep passion for ecological studies and environmental conservation.\n\nEducation:\nChristina holds a Bachelor of Science in Environmental Science from the University of the Witwatersrand.\n\nCourses and Certifications:\nCertified in Environmental Conservation by WWF\nCompleted courses in Climate Change and Biodiversity from Coursera.\n\nSkills:\nEcological analysis\nClimate science\nBiology and biodiversity conservation</string>


</resources>
